https://www.herbsofgrace.com/privacy-policy

My Account
Wish List (0)
0 $0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
Natural Beauty
The Search for the Holy Grail, or, How To Choose the Correct Shade of Foundation
Choosing the Perfect Eye Shadow for YOU
Let’s Get Cheeky, or, Choosing the Correct Blush Color
Mineral Makeup Application Tips
The Benefits of Using Natural Look Mineral Make-up by Herbs of Grace, Inc.
10 Reasons To Use Herbs of Grace Natural Look Mineral Make-up
Natural Look Mineral Make-up Makeovers
Natural Skin Care
Why Buy All Natural Handcrafted Soaps?
Natural Beauty
The Search for the Holy Grail, or, How To Choose the Correct Shade of Foundation
Choosing the Perfect Eye Shadow for YOU
Let’s Get Cheeky, or, Choosing the Correct Blush Color
Mineral Makeup Application Tips
The Benefits of Using Natural Look Mineral Make-up by Herbs of Grace, Inc.
10 Reasons To Use Herbs of Grace Natural Look Mineral Make-up
Natural Look Mineral Make-up Makeovers
Natural Skin Care
Why Buy All Natural Handcrafted Soaps?
Privacy Policy
Herbs of Grace does not sell any of its customer information.
All personal contact information supplied to Herbs of Grace through this
website will be used only for communication regarding: (a) Herbs of
Grace merchandise, (b) orders placed or (c) the Herbs of Grace
Newsletter. Information provided to Herbs of Grace will not be revealed
to any third parties without prior permission except (a) where required
by law, (b) to technically operate this website or (c) to fulfill your
order. See below for more information.
How Herbs of Grace Uses Your Information
Technical operation of this website and order fulfillment
In this instance, Herbs of Grace uses your contact information
to answer questions you may have about our products, take and confirm
your order, process your credit card information with our secure gateway
payment processor and to ship your order.
Personal Greeting. When you log in, your first name will be
included in a personal greeting which is displayed to remind you that
you are logged in. To remove personal greeting, simply click "Log Out"
Online Newsletter
In this instance, Herbs of Grace uses your personal information
to email you our online newsletter, which is published occassionally.
In order to authenticate each subscriber, it is necessary to ask you to
create an account with our online shopping cart system. This helps
ensure that no one gets signed up for our newsletter without their
permission and helps us comply with Federal, State and Local anti-spam
legislation.
All newsletter subscriptions are confirmed-opted in; eg: you
will receive a confirmation email of your account creation. You may
unsubscribe at any time. All newsletters come with unsubscribe
information. When you unsubscribe, your account with Herbs of Grace will
remain intact so that you may shop online, but you will no longer
receive our newsletter. If you wish to remove your account entirely,
please contact us for support.
Tell A Friend
To protect everyone's privacy and prevent abuse, only
registered customers will be allowed to "Tell A Friend" about our
products or about Your Favorites. If you use our Tell A Friend function,
your name and email address will be sent to your friend. Herbs of Grace
absolutely does not use your friend's information other than to send
the email message on your behalf.
If you have received a Tell A Friend email and want to report abuse of this feature, please Contact Us.
Product Reviews
If you submit a product review your first name and last initial
will be displayed along with your review. No other information about
you will be displayed or available with the review, unless you put
personal information in the body of your review (we recommend that you
not include any personal information in your review).
Product Merchandising / Product Recommendations / Best Sellers
General information based on past orders is used to
cross-merchandise our products. However, this is done completely
annonymously so that recommended products cannot be associated with
individual orders.
IP Address
For statisical purposes, your IP Address will be recorded when you interact with our website.
Spam Filter Note
Please make sure your spam filter or firewall will accept email
from Herbs of Grace. If you do not receive a reply to your
communication with us within 48 hours, most likely it was because your
spam filter rejected our email and we were unable to reply to you.
False Identities
Any Herbs of Grace.com user found to be in violation of the
above privacy policy or terms of service will be removed from the
system. Any accounts created with fake or nonsensical names, contact
information, and/or email addresses will be deleted without notice.
Please see our Terms of Service for more information.
About Me
Vanessa Nixon Klein’s story began in the 1990’s when she was able to heal herself of chronic bronchitis through the study of natural medicine, a change to a natural diet and the addition of medicinal herbs. Read Details
Information
Store Locations
Shipping and Returns
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Help & Faq
Contact Us
Extras
